Jamie Henry

sevenjrh@brighthouse.com



321-576-5440



linkedin.com/in/jamie-henry-8ba765154



https://jayhenry07.github.io/

Summary

I am a competitive, and versatile student pursuing a degree in Computer Engineering at the University of Central Florida. I have a passion for computers, technology, video games and I enjoy problem solving and analyzing algorithms. I have experience in Unity and multiple programming languages, such as the skills listed on my profile.

Experience



Server

Olive Garden Sep 2021 - Present (1 month +)



Server

Feb 2016 - Sep 2021 (5 years 8 months)

Education



University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Com 2019 - 2022



Lake-Sumter State College

Associate's degree, General Studies 2017 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp



JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp

Skills

Multitasking • Computer Engineering • Problem Solving • C (Programming Language) • Java • C# • Python (Programming Language) • Data Structures • Time Management • Critical Thinking

Honors & Awards



Excellence in Mathematics - Lake-Sumter State College

Mar 2019